[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Ah, what a beautiful morning.
啊，多么美丽的早晨啊。
Time to check the mail
是时候检查一下邮件了
and see who loves you, Squidward.
看看谁爱你，章鱼哥。
[sighs]
[叹气]
I wonder if I can return
to sender.
我想知道我是否可以回来
至发件人。
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
both: Good morning, Squidward.
两人：早上好，章鱼哥。
Well, I'm going back to bed now.
好吧，我现在要回去睡觉了。
Forever.
永远。
Gah!
嘎！
[both giggling]
[两人都咯咯笑]
Aren't you gonna open your mail?
你不打开你的邮件吗？
Gimme that!
给我那个！
It looks like you already did.
看来你已经这么做了。
Hmm.
[celebratory fanfare]
唔。
[庆祝乐曲]
I won something?
我赢了什么？
But I didn't enter any contest.
但我没有参加任何比赛。
It's an all-expenses-paid trip
这是一次全程自费的旅行
to see beautiful
Bora Bora Bottom.
看到美丽的
波拉波拉岛底部。
We entered it for you,
and only 6,000 times too.
我们为您输入了，
而且也只有6000次。
Wow.
哇。
Me, a winner,
我，一个胜利者，
at a tropical resort.
在一个热带度假胜地。
Let's see,
"The winning family will board
让我们看看，
“获胜的家庭将登机
at Bikini Bottom Airport
and the"...
在 比基尼堡机场
还有“...
Wait a minute.
[shattering]
等一下。
[破碎]
"Winning family"?
“胜利家族”？
Oh, did we forget to mention...
哦，我们是不是忘了说……
[licking]
[舔]
Oh, no.
哦，不。
I cannot believe
我不敢相信
I let you bottom-feeders
talk me into this.
我让你们底层喂食
说服我做这件事。
Oh, it's the least we could
do for a friend like you.
哦，这是我们至少可以做的
为像你这样的朋友做。
I mean, for a dad like you.
我的意思是，对于像你这样的父亲。
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
both: Daddy!
两人：爸爸！
Will you morons... I mean,
children, please!
你们这些白痴会吗...我的意思是，
孩子们，拜托了！
Next.
下一个。
Ha.
哈。
[gasps]
Attention, passengers.
[喘气]
乘客们请注意。
Meet Underwater Air's
big contest winner,
认识水下空气
大赛优胜者，
Squidward Tentacles
and his adorable family.
章鱼哥触手
和他可爱的家人。
Huh, huh.
[cheers and applause]
呵呵。
[欢呼和掌声]
Huh?
- Come on, Dad.
啊？
- 来吧，爸爸。
Let's get a picture
of you and the kids
我们来一张图片
你和孩子们的
for our in-flight magazine.
我们的机上杂志。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[sobs]
[抽泣]
Okay, everybody, say,
"I love my family."
好吧，大家来说说，
“我爱我的家人。”
- I'd rather not.
- [wailing]
- 我宁愿不。
- [哀号]
Say it!
说吧！
both: I love my family.
两人：我爱我的家人。
[shutter clicks]
- [squeals]
[快门声]
- [尖叫声]
[sighs] Hmm.
[叹气] 嗯。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [growls]
- [straining]
- [咆哮]
- [紧张]
I think you're in my seat, Pop.
我想你坐在我的座位上，爸爸。
[straining, sighs]
[紧张，叹气]
Ooh!
- And I'll take the aisle.
哦！
- 我会走过道。
[laughs]
both: ♪ Daddy's in the middle ♪
[笑]
Oh, no.
哦，不。
I am not suffering
a whole flight
我没有痛苦
整个飞行
between you two barnacle brains.
在你们两个藤壶脑之间。
At least give me the aisle.
至少给我留个过道吧。
Excuse me, sir.
对不起，先生。
Are you in your assigned seat?
您在指定的座位上吗？
[knuckles cracking]
[指关节嘎吱作响]
[gulps] Um...
[咽口水] 嗯...
[laughs]
[笑]
[growls]
[咆哮]
Okay, everybody,
please fasten your seat belts
好吧，大家，
请系好安全带
by adjusting
this easy-to-pull strap.
通过调整
这条易于拉动的带子。
Make sure it's nice and tight.
确保它漂亮且紧密。
Wahh!
哇！
And keep your seat
并保持座位
in the upright position.
处于直立位置。
Or else.
否则。
Okay.
好的。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
[babbling]
[胡说]
These look good.
这些看起来不错。
[grunting]
Ooh!
[咕噜声]
哦！
[gasps]
[喘气]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Hey, Patrick, wanna switch
so I can look out the window?
嘿，帕特里克，想换
这样我就可以看看窗外了？
Okay.
Oh, but hurry.
好的。
哦，但是快点。
[straining]
[紧张]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[growls]
[咆哮]
Uh... attention all passengers,
呃...请注意所有乘客，
this is, uh,
your captain speaking.
这是，呃，
你的队长正在讲话。
Please keep your, uh,
seat belts fastened
请保留你的，呃，
系好安全带
as we, uh, gain altitude.
当我们，呃，海拔升高时。
[both babbling]
[两人都胡言乱语]
- Whoa.
- [laughs]
- 哇哦。
- [笑]
Whoa!
哇！
[engine roaring]
[发动机轰鸣]
[chime]
[铃声]
Enjoy your flight.
祝您飞行愉快。
You may now roam
about the, uh, cabin.
您现在可以漫游了
关于，呃，小屋。
Hear that, Squidward?
听到了吗，章鱼哥？
You can take your seat belt
off now.
你可以系好安全带
现在关闭。
Wait!
Untie me!
等待！
给我解开！
[both babbling]
[两人都胡言乱语]
- Ow!
- [grunts] Oh!
- 噢！
- [咕哝]哦！
Oh, boy, a feed bag!
哦，天哪，一个饲料袋！
[inhales]
[吸气]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[air hissing]
- Ow!
[空气嘶嘶声]
- 噢！
Hey!
[passengers groaning]
嘿！
[乘客呻吟声]
- [grumbling]
- [snoring]
- [抱怨]
- [打鼾]
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
Keep it down, will ya?
保持低调，好吗？
I'm tryin' to sleep!
我正想睡觉呢！
Ahh!
啊！
[sighs]
[叹气]
Ugh,
I dreamed I was in the ocean,
呃，
我梦见自己在大海里
and now I gotta pee!
现在我要尿尿！
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
哦哦哦哦哦
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Huh?
啊？
Uh, huh?
呃，嗯？
Uh... ah!
- Can I help you
呃……啊！
- 我可以帮你吗
with something?
与某事？
Yeah, I gotta use a bathroom!
是啊，我要上厕所！
[grunts]
- Ahh!
[咕哝]
- 啊！
Rude.
I was here first.
粗鲁的。
我先来的。
Wah!
哇！
Oh!
哦！
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Hey, buddy, what happened
to the other flight attendant?
嘿，伙计，发生了什么事
给另一位空姐？
She's in the bathroom.
她在浴室里。
- Ahh!
- See?
- 啊！
- 看？
Whoa!
哇！
Ooh.
哦。
Ahh!
啊！
Oh.
哦。
[sighs]
[叹气]
[straining]
[紧张]
[growls] Huh?
[咆哮]啊？
The flight attendants
will save me.
空乘人员
会救我的。
[strains]
[菌株]
Just need
to hit that call button.
只需要
点击呼叫按钮。
[grunts]
[button chimes]
[咕哝]
[按钮铃声]
[sighs]
[叹气]
Good evening, Mr. Sir!
晚上好，先生！
Fresh coffee?
新鲜咖啡？
What?
什么？
Patrick, where are the real
flight attendants?
帕特里克，真正的人在哪里？
空姐？
They've been in the bathroom
for a while.
他们已经在浴室里了
有一段时间了。
I think they had
too much coffee.
我认为他们有
咖啡太多了。
Now how about that coffee?
现在那杯咖啡怎么样？
No, I don't want... ahh!
不，我不想……啊！
[gurgling]
[淙淙]
Wow, Squidward,
you really like coffee!
哇，章鱼哥，
你真的很喜欢咖啡！
Whoa!
哇！
[intercom chimes]
- Uh, folks.
[对讲机铃声]
- 呃，各位。
Sorry about that turbulence.
对这次动荡感到抱歉。
[gasps]
[喘气]
Wow, Patrick.
哇，帕特里克。
They made you
a flight attendant?
他们让你
空姐？
Yeah-huh.
Hey, you wanna be one too?
是啊哈。
嘿，你也想成为其中一员吗？
[gasps] Yeah.
[喘气]是的。
♪ ♪
♪♪
Ah.
啊。
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
[gasps]
Our apologies, sir.
[喘气]
我们很抱歉，先生。
Let's get you dried off.
让我们把你擦干。
[air whooshing]
[空气呼啸]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Whoa!
哇！
[crash]
[碰撞]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[spluttering]
[溅射]
Huh?
I'm free.
啊？
我有空了。
I'm free!
我自由了！
[gasps]
- Snack time!
[喘气]
- 零食时间！
[babbling]
[胡说]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Whee!
哎哟！
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Whoa!
哇！
[groans]
[呻吟]
That's it!
就是这样！
I am filing a complaint
with the captain.
我正在提出投诉
与船长。
Roll me to the front
of the plane.
把我滚到前面
飞机的。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Huh?
啊？
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
Are you enjoying your flight?
您的飞行愉快吗？
No, I am not.
不，我不是。
These two have been nothing
but trouble since we took off.
这两个本来就没什么
但自从我们起飞以来就遇到了麻烦。
And now they've replaced
the flight attendants.
现在他们已经取代了
空乘人员。
Uh, what did they do with them?
呃，他们对它们做了什么？
I just opened
the bathroom door, Captain.
我刚打开
浴室的门，船长。
Like this.
像这样。
Oh!
[both groaning]
哦！
[两人都呻吟]
both: Ahh.
两人：啊。
Ahh!
啊！
Oh.
哦。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Huh?
啊？
There's no one flying the plane!
飞机上没人啊！
Ahh!
[alarm bells blare]
啊！
[警钟长鸣]
Ahh!
啊！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
What are we gonna do?
我们要做什么？
Oh, we're gonna crash.
哦，我们要崩溃了。
Uh, uh,
I guess I can figure this out.
呃，呃，
我想我能弄清楚这一点。
Yeah, how hard could it be?
是啊，这能有多难呢？
[panel beeping rapidly]
[面板快速发出蜂鸣声]
Squidward, trust your instincts.
章鱼哥，相信你的直觉。
I suppose, uh...
我想，呃...
[beeps]
[嘟嘟声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
Look, Squidward,
we're almost there!
看，章鱼哥，
我们快到了！
Now all you gotta do
is land this thing!
现在你要做的就是
就是土地这个东西！
And not kill everyone.
并且不杀掉所有人。
both: Squidward,
Squidward, Squidward!
两者：章鱼哥，
章鱼哥，章鱼哥！
[screaming]
[alarm beeping]
[尖叫]
[警报声]
[all screaming]
- Squidward!
[所有人尖叫]
- 章鱼哥！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
♪ ♪
♪♪
both: Squidward, Squidward!
- [groaning]
两人：章鱼哥，章鱼哥！
- [呻吟]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[screaming]
[尖叫]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Ahh!
啊！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Hmm?
唔？
[both cheer]
[两人欢呼]
Yay, Squidward!
耶，章鱼哥！
Huh?
Bora Bora Bottom!
啊？
波拉波拉岛底部！
Hmm.
唔。
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
Uh, attention, passengers,
呃，乘客们请注意，
this is your new captain speaking.
这是你们的新队长在讲话。
We have arrived
at beautiful Bora Bora Bottom.
我们已经到了
在美丽的波拉波拉岛底部。
Ha... huh?
[engine whirring]
哈……啊？
[引擎的呼呼声]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Wait a minute!
等一下！
I thought I stopped this thing!
我以为我阻止了这件事！
[laughs]
Squidward, look!
[笑]
It was on auto-pilot
the whole time.
它处于自动驾驶状态
一直以来。
Yay, Squidward!
耶，章鱼哥！
You did nothing!
你什么也没做！
[both laugh]
- No, no!
[两人都笑了]
- 不，不！
I need to get off this plane
and enjoy the resort!
我需要下飞机
并享受度假村！
Now why would you wanna do that?
现在你为什么要这么做？
[laughs]
[笑]
You won a trip
to see Bora Bora Bottom,
你赢得了一次旅行
去看波拉波拉岛底部，
not stay there, silly.
不要呆在那里，傻瓜。
And there it goes.
就这样。
Huh?
啊？
[sighs]
Life is funny, isn't it?
[叹气]
生活很有趣，不是吗？
♪ ♪
♪♪
[chimes]
[编钟]
Ahh!
啊！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Ow!
噢！
This is your
flight attendant speaking.
这是你的
空乘人员讲话。
Looks like we're experiencing
some headwinds,
看起来我们正在经历
一些逆风，
and the present estimate
for our return flight
和目前的估计
回程航班
to Bikini Bottom is 24 hours!
到 Bikini Bottom 需要 24 小时！
[both laugh]
[都笑了]
No!
不！